countdowntopregnancy.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy policy - Countdown to pregnancy

CountdownToPregnancy.com acknowledges that privacy is a concern for our Web site visitors due to it's sensitive and personal nature and this policy statement explains how we manage information provided to us by our Web visitors.

All information that is provided to us through our Web site is treated with respect and confidentiality, and we are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust.

There are certain actions and areas of the site that require you to provide personal information, such as: 

  * becoming a member
  * sending an email on the 'contact us' page

Any time you provide personal information, you should be mindful of the terms of this privacy policy, as it will govern our use of the information you have provided.

In order to gain access to certain areas of our site, you may choose to provide information. If you do submit information to us, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was submitted. Personal information you provide is stored in a secure location and is accessible only by designated staff.

Other than as described in this privacy policy, or as may be necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of our organization or others, or as may be necessary to comply with applicable law, CountdownToPregnancy.com will not give or sell the personal information you provide online.

Only information you select to have displayed (using your My Account or My Profile settings) will be displayed in these locations.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Interest-based online advertising and Google analytics

This section of the Privacy policy provides details about interest-based online advertising (also called "targeted advertising", "remarketing", or "behavioral advertising"), Google Analytics, and your choices with respect to this type of advertising.

We use Google Analytics' 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender and interests to better understand the behavior of our visitors and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain ads on this website or other websites because we contract with Google and other similar companies to target our ads based on information we or they have collected, including information that was collected through automated means (such as cookies). These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads' preferences at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. Because those opt-out and preference control pages are specific to the individual browser used to visit it, and because that page is not operated by the Countdown Family Inc., we are unable to perform the opt-outs on your behalf.

#### Cookie policy

This website uses cookies. Please visit our Cookie policy page to learn more.

#### Contact us

If you have any questions about our privacy policies, please visit our contact page.
